<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Shop &#8211; doKan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/shop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 12:21:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Pearson Higher Nationals in Computing Book</title>
		<link>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/pearson-higher-nationals-in-computing-book/</link>
					<comments>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/pearson-higher-nationals-in-computing-book/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[doKan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/?post_type=product#038;p=59</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The <strong>Pearson BTEC Higher Nationals in Computing</strong> are world-class Level 4 and 5 qualifications.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <strong>Pearson BTEC Higher Nationals in Computing</strong> are world-class Level 4 and 5 qualifications. Developed in partnership with input from employers, professional bodies, and vendors, these qualifications equip students with the right skills and competencies for the workplace or further higher education study. They address the increasing need for high-quality professional and technical education pathways in computing</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/pearson-higher-nationals-in-computing-book/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fleece Jacket</title>
		<link>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/fleece-jacket/</link>
					<comments>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/fleece-jacket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[doKan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/?post_type=product#038;p=46</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stay cozy and stylish with our Fleece Jacket. Designed for warmth and comfort, this versatile piece is perfect for layering in cooler weather. With its soft fleece construction and classic silhouette, it's a must-have addition to any wardrobe.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embrace the chilly seasons in style with our Fleece Jacket, a quintessential outerwear piece that seamlessly blends warmth, comfort, and fashion. Crafted from high-quality fleece material, this jacket offers a plush feel against your skin while providing exceptional insulation to keep you cozy on brisk days. Its classic design features a full-length zipper, convenient pockets, and a relaxed fit that allows for easy layering over your favorite sweaters or shirts. Whether you&#8217;re exploring the great outdoors, running errands in town, or simply lounging at home, this versatile jacket is your go-to companion for all your cold-weather adventures. Elevate your winter wardrobe with our Fleece Jacket and experience the perfect combination of style and functionality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/fleece-jacket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Short Sleeve T-shirt</title>
		<link>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/short-sleeve-tshirt/</link>
					<comments>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/short-sleeve-tshirt/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[doKan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 13:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/?post_type=product#038;p=23</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elevate your casual wardrobe with our Short Sleeve T-shirt. Crafted from soft, breathable fabric, this versatile piece offers comfort and style for everyday wear. Available in a range of colors, it's perfect for layering or wearing solo.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Introducing our Short Sleeve T-shirt, the ultimate staple for effortless style and comfort. Crafted with the modern individual in mind, this essential piece combines superior quality with timeless design. Made from premium, lightweight fabric, it offers a soft and breathable feel that keeps you comfortable all day long. Whether you&#8217;re running errands, meeting friends, or lounging at home, this versatile tee is your go-to choose. Its classic silhouette and relaxed fit make it easy to pair with jeans, shorts, or skirts, while the variety of available colors ensures there&#8217;s an option for every mood and occasion. Add a touch of casual elegance to your wardrobe with our Short Sleeve T-shirt and experience the perfect blend of fashion and functionality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/short-sleeve-tshirt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Pixel 8 Pro/ 256GB 12GB RAM</title>
		<link>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/google-pixel-8-pro-256gb-12gb-ram/</link>
					<comments>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/google-pixel-8-pro-256gb-12gb-ram/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[doKan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 13:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/?post_type=product#038;p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pixel 8 Pro’s 6.7-inch Super Actua display features our brightest display yet. So even in direct sunlight, you’ll love how true-to-life your Ultra HDR images look. It also has a matte glass back with a polished aluminum frame and comes in three colors: Porcelain, Bay and Obsidian]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Pixel 8 Pro’s 6.7-inch Super Actua display features our brightest display yet. So even in direct sunlight, you’ll love how true-to-life your Ultra HDR images look. It also has a matte glass back with a polished aluminum frame and comes in three colors: Porcelain, Bay and Obsidian</li>
</ul>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-17 aligncenter" src="https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Pixel_8_Pro_in_Bay.max-936x936.format-webp.png" alt="" width="542" height="298" /></p>
<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">Pixel 8 Pro is the all-pro phone engineered by Google; it’s super-fast, powerful, and secure, with the new Google Tensor G3 chip that’s custom-designed with Google AI for cutting-edge photo and video features and smarter ways to help.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">Unlocked Android 5G phone gives you the flexibility to change carriers and choose your own data plan; it works with Google Fi, Verizon, T-Mobile, AT&amp;T, and other major carriers.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">With the most refined design yet, Pixel 8 Pro has an immersive, 6.7-inch Super Actua display that makes everything sharp; the refresh rate intelligently adjusts between 1 and 120Hz for responsive performance.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">Google Pixel 8 Pro has four updated pro-level cameras with Pixel’s best zoom ever; Pro controls unlock advanced settings and support full-resolution photos.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">The Pixel 8 Pro camera gives you amazing video quality; it records sharp, smooth videos, even in dimly lit places; and Audio Magic Eraser uses Google AI to reduce distracting noises, like cars and wind</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">Pixel’s Adaptive Battery can last over 24 hours; when Extreme Battery Saver is turned on, it can last up to 72 hours, and it charges faster than ever.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">Pixel 8 Pro can notify first responders in an emergency and share your location and can even detect if you’ve been in a severe car crash; if you’re unable to respond, your Pixel phone can call emergency services and notify your chosen contacts.</span></li>
</ul>
<div class="a-row a-expander-container a-expander-inline-container">
<div class="a-expander-content a-expander-extend-content a-expander-content-expanded" aria-expanded="true">
<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-none">
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">With powerful security features, your Pixel phone helps keep your info safe; Google Tensor G3, VPN by Google One, and the Titan M2 security chip give your Pixel multiple layers of security</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">Switching to Pixel is easy; just connect your old phone to your new Pixel and transfer contacts, photos, messages, apps, and more in about 30 minutes</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://suyog-gautam.github.io/doKan.com/product/google-pixel-8-pro-256gb-12gb-ram/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
